<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Health - Latest News</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/news/ind/health/</link>
<description>Health - Latest News (Press Releases) - Read news before it's news</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<ttl>3600</ttl>
<item>
<title>Carolina Core Wellness Showcases New Community to Health &amp; Wellness Professionals in the heart of NC</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12902716-carolina-core-wellness-showcases-new-community-to-health-wellness-professionals-in-the-heart-of-nc.html</link>
<description>The Triad has many impressive local attractions such as the Greensboro Science Center, Reynolda House, and Greensboro Coliseum, but aren't we missing a destination on this scale that supports the overall health and wellness of the Triad's residents? None.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 20:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Home Helpers San Mateo Receives 2021 Best of Home Care® – Leader in Experience Award</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12902723-home-helpers-san-mateo-receives-2021-best-of-home-care-leader-in-experience-award.html</link>
<description>Home Helpers of San Mateo County announced today that it received the distinguished Best of Home Care –Leader in Experience Award from Home Care Pulse, the leading firm in quality assurance for home care.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:52:27 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dr. Maiysha Clairborne: 3 Steps To Master Your Mind With NLP</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12902451-dr-maiysha-clairborne-3-steps-to-master-your-mind-with-nlp.html</link>
<description>Have you ever met someone who can just say what they want and it seems to magically happen? Do you know someone like this? Someone who seems to have no trouble manifesting things in their life whether it be new relationships, more money, the perfect job.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 14:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stroudwater Associates Further Increases Support for Rural &amp; Community Healthcare</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12901831-stroudwater-associates-further-increases-support-for-rural-community-healthcare.html</link>
<description>Despite continuing challenges from the COVID-19 pandemic, the rural and community healthcare consulting firm continued to deliver strategic, operational, financial, and clinical expertise to healthcare leaders across the nation</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:18:17 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The OCD Recovery Project continues helping sufferers identify and recover from OCD</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12901180-the-ocd-recovery-project-continues-helping-sufferers-identify-and-recover-from-ocd.html</link>
<description>The OCD Test has rebranded to The OCD Recovery Project while providing new industry-leading OCD test</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 20:12:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pharma time-to-market reduced thanks to more efficient submission document publishing services</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12899951-pharma-time-to-market-reduced-thanks-to-more-efficient-submission-document-publishing-services.html</link>
<description>PharmaLex, a leading provider of specialized services for the pharmaceutical, biotech and medical device industries, chose DocShifter to simplify and accelerate the generation of compliant, submission-ready PDF documents for their 1000's of clients.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:39:25 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Nurses Rock Pacific Palisades</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12898760-the-nurses-rock-pacific-palisades.html</link>
<description>Fundraising Gala Held At Terranea Resort To Drive Resources For 2022 Education Center</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:35:43 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HOPE Sheds Light hosts successful 3rd Annual Evening of HOPE</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12897219-hope-sheds-light-hosts-successful-3rd-annual-evening-of-hope.html</link>
<description>The Ocean County nonprofit kicks off Circle of HOPE initiative for 2022.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 19:43:24 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HD Physical Therapy Offers Tips to Avoid Aches &amp; Pains this Holiday Season</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12896524-hd-physical-therapy-offers-tips-to-avoid-aches-pains-this-holiday-season.html</link>
<description>2021 has flown by and the holiday season is here. Unfortunately this can mean added stress, plus aches and pains. Here are just a few tips to stay on track with your health over the holidays while still enjoying all that the season has to offer.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 19:27:33 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Washington Home Care LLC Marks Second Anniversary With Influx Of Durable Medical Equipment Donations</title>
<link>https://www.prlog.org/12896206-washington-home-care-llc-marks-second-anniversary-with-influx-of-durable-medical-equipment-donations.html</link>
<description>Sara Guillemette, the founder of Washington Home Care LLC in Washington, Connecticut, marks the second anniversary of having opened December 21, 2019.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>